{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868841692","data":{"timestamp":" 946868841691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868850628","data":{"timestamp":" 946868850627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868850858","data":{"timestamp":" 946868850857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868851821","data":{"timestamp":" 946868851821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868853095","data":{"timestamp":" 946868853095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868855934","data":{"timestamp":" 946868855934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868856777","data":{"timestamp":" 946868856777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868857090","data":{"timestamp":" 946868857090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868858322","data":{"timestamp":" 946868858322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868861793","data":{"timestamp":" 946868861792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868862776","data":{"timestamp":" 946868862775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868863028","data":{"timestamp":" 946868863028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868863970","data":{"timestamp":" 946868863970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868866788","data":{"timestamp":" 946868866788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868867821","data":{"timestamp":" 946868867821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868868293","data":{"timestamp":" 946868868293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868872793","data":{"timestamp":" 946868872793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868872845","data":{"timestamp":" 946868872845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 3c451eb3-cbf2-4402-af53-5f87b0a2782f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868889507","data":{"timestamp":" 946868889507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868889739","data":{"timestamp":" 946868889738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868890702","data":{"timestamp":" 946868890702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868891983","data":{"timestamp":" 946868891983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868894940","data":{"timestamp":" 946868894939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868895784","data":{"timestamp":" 946868895783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868896104","data":{"timestamp":" 946868896103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868897347","data":{"timestamp":" 946868897346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868900891","data":{"timestamp":" 946868900889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868901888","data":{"timestamp":" 946868901887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868902151","data":{"timestamp":" 946868902150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868903102","data":{"timestamp":" 946868903102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868905951","data":{"timestamp":" 946868905951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868906986","data":{"timestamp":" 946868906986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868907469","data":{"timestamp":" 946868907467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868912021","data":{"timestamp":" 946868912020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868912106","data":{"timestamp":" 946868912106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 65bfb6d7-a10b-4312-9947-3710455126ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868922604","data":{"timestamp":" 946868922603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868922831","data":{"timestamp":" 946868922831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868923794","data":{"timestamp":" 946868923794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868925066","data":{"timestamp":" 946868925066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868927900","data":{"timestamp":" 946868927900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868928742","data":{"timestamp":" 946868928742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868929055","data":{"timestamp":" 946868929055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868930288","data":{"timestamp":" 946868930288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868933761","data":{"timestamp":" 946868933761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868934743","data":{"timestamp":" 946868934743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868934996","data":{"timestamp":" 946868934996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868935939","data":{"timestamp":" 946868935938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868938759","data":{"timestamp":" 946868938759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868939803","data":{"timestamp":" 946868939802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868940287","data":{"timestamp":" 946868940286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868944686","data":{"timestamp":" 946868944685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868944739","data":{"timestamp":" 946868944739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" ef2ac3a4-8200-4115-a8c0-d4b0273974ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868955348","data":{"timestamp":" 946868955348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868955579","data":{"timestamp":" 946868955578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868956553","data":{"timestamp":" 946868956553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868957840","data":{"timestamp":" 946868957838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868960791","data":{"timestamp":" 946868960791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868961648","data":{"timestamp":" 946868961647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868961967","data":{"timestamp":" 946868961966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868963214","data":{"timestamp":" 946868963213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868966808","data":{"timestamp":" 946868966807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868967802","data":{"timestamp":" 946868967801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868968064","data":{"timestamp":" 946868968064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868969019","data":{"timestamp":" 946868969018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868971937","data":{"timestamp":" 946868971936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868972983","data":{"timestamp":" 946868972982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868973466","data":{"timestamp":" 946868973465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868978013","data":{"timestamp":" 946868978012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868978120","data":{"timestamp":" 946868978119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" c96d3223-afdb-44e9-9d1d-4059eb8f5464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868993729","data":{"timestamp":" 946868993729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868993961","data":{"timestamp":" 946868993960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868994932","data":{"timestamp":" 946868994932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868996214","data":{"timestamp":" 946868996213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868999174","data":{"timestamp":" 946868999174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869000029","data":{"timestamp":" 946869000028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869000351","data":{"timestamp":" 946869000351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869001596","data":{"timestamp":" 946869001596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869005137","data":{"timestamp":" 946869005137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869006135","data":{"timestamp":" 946869006133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869006398","data":{"timestamp":" 946869006398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869007354","data":{"timestamp":" 946869007353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869010248","data":{"timestamp":" 946869010247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869011290","data":{"timestamp":" 946869011289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869011770","data":{"timestamp":" 946869011770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869016328","data":{"timestamp":" 946869016327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869016454","data":{"timestamp":" 946869016454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869034819","data":{"timestamp":" 946869034819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 24dbb386-001d-4c97-a598-ae1846aa63a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869049739","data":{"timestamp":" 946869049739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869050292","data":{"timestamp":" 946869050291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869051292","data":{"timestamp":" 946869051291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869051875","data":{"timestamp":" 946869051874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869052604","data":{"timestamp":" 946869052603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869059343","data":{"timestamp":" 946869059343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869060876","data":{"timestamp":" 946869060875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869062294","data":{"timestamp":" 946869062293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869063798","data":{"timestamp":" 946869063796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869065214","data":{"timestamp":" 946869065213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869066049","data":{"timestamp":" 946869066048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869068094","data":{"timestamp":" 946869068093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869068386","data":{"timestamp":" 946869068385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869069074","data":{"timestamp":" 946869069074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869069671","data":{"timestamp":" 946869069671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869070528","data":{"timestamp":" 946869070527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869071357","data":{"timestamp":" 946869071357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869071798","data":{"timestamp":" 946869071797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869072679","data":{"timestamp":" 946869072679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869074030","data":{"timestamp":" 946869074030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869075272","data":{"timestamp":" 946869075271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869075292","data":{"timestamp":" 946869075291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869075740","data":{"timestamp":" 946869075740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869076328","data":{"timestamp":" 946869076327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869078810","data":{"timestamp":" 946869078810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869079053","data":{"timestamp":" 946869079053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869080796","data":{"timestamp":" 946869080796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869081600","data":{"timestamp":" 946869081600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869082507","data":{"timestamp":" 946869082506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869083605","data":{"timestamp":" 946869083605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869084090","data":{"timestamp":" 946869084090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869084499","data":{"timestamp":" 946869084499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869086508","data":{"timestamp":" 946869086508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869086512","data":{"timestamp":" 946869086511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869086514","data":{"timestamp":" 946869086514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869086890","data":{"timestamp":" 946869086890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869087511","data":{"timestamp":" 946869087511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869088787","data":{"timestamp":" 946869088786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869091011","data":{"timestamp":" 946869091010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869091806","data":{"timestamp":" 946869091806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869092904","data":{"timestamp":" 946869092904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869093541","data":{"timestamp":" 946869093541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869096409","data":{"timestamp":" 946869096409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869096948","data":{"timestamp":" 946869096947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" START_MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869098411","data":{"timestamp":" 946869098410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869100043","data":{"timestamp":" 946869100042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869100525","data":{"timestamp":" 946869100524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869100603","data":{"timestamp":" 946869100603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869102923","data":{"timestamp":" 946869102923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869103215","data":{"timestamp":" 946869103215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869103909","data":{"timestamp":" 946869103909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869104155","data":{"timestamp":" 946869104154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869104600","data":{"timestamp":" 946869104599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869105279","data":{"timestamp":" 946869105278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869105695","data":{"timestamp":" 946869105694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869106696","data":{"timestamp":" 946869106695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869108103","data":{"timestamp":" 946869108102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869108622","data":{"timestamp":" 946869108621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869109924","data":{"timestamp":" 946869109924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869110768","data":{"timestamp":" 946869110767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869111728","data":{"timestamp":" 946869111727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869113786","data":{"timestamp":" 946869113786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869114505","data":{"timestamp":" 946869114505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869114508","data":{"timestamp":" 946869114508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869115206","data":{"timestamp":" 946869115206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869116011","data":{"timestamp":" 946869116011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869116100","data":{"timestamp":" 946869116100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869117506","data":{"timestamp":" 946869117506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" START_BILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869118527","data":{"timestamp":" 946869118527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869120016","data":{"timestamp":" 946869120015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869121481","data":{"timestamp":" 946869121481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869122507","data":{"timestamp":" 946869122506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" START_MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869124173","data":{"timestamp":" 946869124173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869125778","data":{"timestamp":" 946869125777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869126562","data":{"timestamp":" 946869126562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869127705","data":{"timestamp":" 946869127705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869129245","data":{"timestamp":" 946869129244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869130916","data":{"timestamp":" 946869130916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869131755","data":{"timestamp":" 946869131754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869133703","data":{"timestamp":" 946869133702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869135282","data":{"timestamp":" 946869135282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869135781","data":{"timestamp":" 946869135781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" START_MREMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869139613","data":{"timestamp":" 946869139613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869141659","data":{"timestamp":" 946869141658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869142877","data":{"timestamp":" 946869142877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869143782","data":{"timestamp":" 946869143782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869144286","data":{"timestamp":" 946869144286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869145376","data":{"timestamp":" 946869145376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUNIA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869146096","data":{"timestamp":" 946869146095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869148689","data":{"timestamp":" 946869148688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869150675","data":{"timestamp":" 946869150675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869151284","data":{"timestamp":" 946869151284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869152047","data":{"timestamp":" 946869152047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869152706","data":{"timestamp":" 946869152706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUNIA"," userResponse":" START_KUJIVUNIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869154167","data":{"timestamp":" 946869154167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUNIA"," userResponse":" START_KUJIVUNIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869155956","data":{"timestamp":" 946869155955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUNIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869156916","data":{"timestamp":" 946869156915"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869158851","data":{"timestamp":" 946869158851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869159627","data":{"timestamp":" 946869159627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869159843","data":{"timestamp":" 946869159842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869160445","data":{"timestamp":" 946869160444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869161314","data":{"timestamp":" 946869161314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869162459","data":{"timestamp":" 946869162459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869163013","data":{"timestamp":" 946869163013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869164105","data":{"timestamp":" 946869164105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWACHA"," userResponse":" ALIMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869164759","data":{"timestamp":" 946869164759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869165639","data":{"timestamp":" 946869165638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869166638","data":{"timestamp":" 946869166638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869167319","data":{"timestamp":" 946869167318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869167936","data":{"timestamp":" 946869167935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869168417","data":{"timestamp":" 946869168417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869169206","data":{"timestamp":" 946869169205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAMA"," userResponse":" KUKAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869169748","data":{"timestamp":" 946869169747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869169775","data":{"timestamp":" 946869169775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869172373","data":{"timestamp":" 946869172372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869173170","data":{"timestamp":" 946869173170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869173669","data":{"timestamp":" 946869173669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869174183","data":{"timestamp":" 946869174183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869174992","data":{"timestamp":" 946869174991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869176081","data":{"timestamp":" 946869176081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869176587","data":{"timestamp":" 946869176586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869178422","data":{"timestamp":" 946869178422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWACHA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMWACHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869180516","data":{"timestamp":" 946869180515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWACHA"," userResponse":" ALIMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869182012","data":{"timestamp":" 946869182012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869182830","data":{"timestamp":" 946869182830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869183784","data":{"timestamp":" 946869183783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869185466","data":{"timestamp":" 946869185465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869186928","data":{"timestamp":" 946869186928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869187736","data":{"timestamp":" 946869187735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869189142","data":{"timestamp":" 946869189142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869189455","data":{"timestamp":" 946869189455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869190566","data":{"timestamp":" 946869190565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAMA"," userResponse":" KUKAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869191851","data":{"timestamp":" 946869191850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869191974","data":{"timestamp":" 946869191974"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869194051","data":{"timestamp":" 946869194050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869194325","data":{"timestamp":" 946869194324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869195137","data":{"timestamp":" 946869195137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869195795","data":{"timestamp":" 946869195794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869197124","data":{"timestamp":" 946869197123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHIA"," userResponse":" KUMWACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869197880","data":{"timestamp":" 946869197880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869198126","data":{"timestamp":" 946869198126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869198908","data":{"timestamp":" 946869198907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869199855","data":{"timestamp":" 946869199855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869200597","data":{"timestamp":" 946869200593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMA"," userResponse":" PEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869201596","data":{"timestamp":" 946869201595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869201680","data":{"timestamp":" 946869201680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869202238","data":{"timestamp":" 946869202238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869204668","data":{"timestamp":" 946869204668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869204832","data":{"timestamp":" 946869204831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869205367","data":{"timestamp":" 946869205367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" START_KAWAIDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869206913","data":{"timestamp":" 946869206913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869206919","data":{"timestamp":" 946869206919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869208947","data":{"timestamp":" 946869208947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHIA"," userResponse":" START_KUMWACHIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869209999","data":{"timestamp":" 946869209998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHIA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869211823","data":{"timestamp":" 946869211822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869212121","data":{"timestamp":" 946869212121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869213056","data":{"timestamp":" 946869213056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869213429","data":{"timestamp":" 946869213429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869214149","data":{"timestamp":" 946869214149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869214956","data":{"timestamp":" 946869214956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" START_MAHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869216468","data":{"timestamp":" 946869216467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" PEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869218330","data":{"timestamp":" 946869218330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869219210","data":{"timestamp":" 946869219209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMA"," userResponse":" PEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869220118","data":{"timestamp":" 946869220118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869220503","data":{"timestamp":" 946869220502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869220894","data":{"timestamp":" 946869220893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869223179","data":{"timestamp":" 946869223178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869223692","data":{"timestamp":" 946869223692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869224498","data":{"timestamp":" 946869224498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869225328","data":{"timestamp":" 946869225328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBAKI"," userResponse":" ALIBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869226178","data":{"timestamp":" 946869226178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869227558","data":{"timestamp":" 946869227558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869227815","data":{"timestamp":" 946869227815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869228653","data":{"timestamp":" 946869228653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869229391","data":{"timestamp":" 946869229391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869230053","data":{"timestamp":" 946869230052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869230721","data":{"timestamp":" 946869230721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869231407","data":{"timestamp":" 946869231407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869232129","data":{"timestamp":" 946869232129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869234168","data":{"timestamp":" 946869234167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869234672","data":{"timestamp":" 946869234672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869235371","data":{"timestamp":" 946869235371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869236574","data":{"timestamp":" 946869236573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBAKI"," userResponse":" ALIBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869237065","data":{"timestamp":" 946869237064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" START_CHUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869239499","data":{"timestamp":" 946869239499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869240589","data":{"timestamp":" 946869240589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869240795","data":{"timestamp":" 946869240795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869241729","data":{"timestamp":" 946869241729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" START_KUNYWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869242709","data":{"timestamp":" 946869242708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869244271","data":{"timestamp":" 946869244271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869245530","data":{"timestamp":" 946869245530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869246056","data":{"timestamp":" 946869246056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869246770","data":{"timestamp":" 946869246770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869248851","data":{"timestamp":" 946869248851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869248957","data":{"timestamp":" 946869248957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869251187","data":{"timestamp":" 946869251185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869252674","data":{"timestamp":" 946869252673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANGEKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869253350","data":{"timestamp":" 946869253349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869253536","data":{"timestamp":" 946869253535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869254235","data":{"timestamp":" 946869254234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLEA"," userResponse":" KUMLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869256254","data":{"timestamp":" 946869256253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" START_MAMAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869257119","data":{"timestamp":" 946869257119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869258693","data":{"timestamp":" 946869258692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869259284","data":{"timestamp":" 946869259284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869260625","data":{"timestamp":" 946869260625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANGEKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869262124","data":{"timestamp":" 946869262123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" START_CHUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869265692","data":{"timestamp":" 946869265691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869266797","data":{"timestamp":" 946869266797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869267402","data":{"timestamp":" 946869267402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLEA"," userResponse":" KUMLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869269676","data":{"timestamp":" 946869269675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869270455","data":{"timestamp":" 946869270455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869271122","data":{"timestamp":" 946869271122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869271353","data":{"timestamp":" 946869271353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869272019","data":{"timestamp":" 946869272019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869273328","data":{"timestamp":" 946869273327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIPATIKANA"," userResponse":" KILIPATIKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869274001","data":{"timestamp":" 946869274001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKIWA"," userResponse":" KIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869274630","data":{"timestamp":" 946869274629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869277092","data":{"timestamp":" 946869277091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869277599","data":{"timestamp":" 946869277599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869278508","data":{"timestamp":" 946869278507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869278687","data":{"timestamp":" 946869278687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869278999","data":{"timestamp":" 946869278998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" START_MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869282662","data":{"timestamp":" 946869282662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869284353","data":{"timestamp":" 946869284352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869286843","data":{"timestamp":" 946869286843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIPATIKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869289257","data":{"timestamp":" 946869289257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869290874","data":{"timestamp":" 946869290874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869292932","data":{"timestamp":" 946869292932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869294055","data":{"timestamp":" 946869294055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILISHANGAZA"," userResponse":" ILISHANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869294979","data":{"timestamp":" 946869294979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869297624","data":{"timestamp":" 946869297623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869298754","data":{"timestamp":" 946869298754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILISHANGAZA"," userResponse":" START_ILISHANGAZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869301470","data":{"timestamp":" 946869301470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILISHANGAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869303544","data":{"timestamp":" 946869303544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869305922","data":{"timestamp":" 946869305921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869306721","data":{"timestamp":" 946869306720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869307558","data":{"timestamp":" 946869307557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869308825","data":{"timestamp":" 946869308824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEJUA"," userResponse":" ALIYEJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869309448","data":{"timestamp":" 946869309448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869310498","data":{"timestamp":" 946869310498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869311205","data":{"timestamp":" 946869311204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869314437","data":{"timestamp":" 946869314437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869316273","data":{"timestamp":" 946869316273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869318491","data":{"timestamp":" 946869318491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869320436","data":{"timestamp":" 946869320436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869322293","data":{"timestamp":" 946869322293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869325228","data":{"timestamp":" 946869325228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869327177","data":{"timestamp":" 946869327177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869329892","data":{"timestamp":" 946869329891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869330437","data":{"timestamp":" 946869330436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869331799","data":{"timestamp":" 946869331798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWARIFU"," userResponse":" ALIMWARIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869332455","data":{"timestamp":" 946869332454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869333400","data":{"timestamp":" 946869333399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUKIO"," userResponse":" MATUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869333954","data":{"timestamp":" 946869333953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869336642","data":{"timestamp":" 946869336642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869338510","data":{"timestamp":" 946869338510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869340536","data":{"timestamp":" 946869340535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWARIFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869342698","data":{"timestamp":" 946869342698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869344854","data":{"timestamp":" 946869344854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUKIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869347042","data":{"timestamp":" 946869347042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869349162","data":{"timestamp":" 946869349160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869350023","data":{"timestamp":" 946869350023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMUA"," userResponse":" AKAAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869351332","data":{"timestamp":" 946869351331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPELELEZA"," userResponse":" KUPELELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869352250","data":{"timestamp":" 946869352249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869352926","data":{"timestamp":" 946869352926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APATE"," userResponse":" APATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869353714","data":{"timestamp":" 946869353713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" UKWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869354600","data":{"timestamp":" 946869354599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMILI"," userResponse":" KAMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869357590","data":{"timestamp":" 946869357590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869360773","data":{"timestamp":" 946869360773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869362909","data":{"timestamp":" 946869362909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPELELEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869364814","data":{"timestamp":" 946869364813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869366471","data":{"timestamp":" 946869366471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APATE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869368866","data":{"timestamp":" 946869368866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869371158","data":{"timestamp":" 946869371158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869373378","data":{"timestamp":" 946869373377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869374076","data":{"timestamp":" 946869374075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869375250","data":{"timestamp":" 946869375250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869375987","data":{"timestamp":" 946869375987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869376076","data":{"timestamp":" 946869376076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869376753","data":{"timestamp":" 946869376753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869377330","data":{"timestamp":" 946869377329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869378567","data":{"timestamp":" 946869378567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHANGAA"," userResponse":" AKASHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869379222","data":{"timestamp":" 946869379222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869379986","data":{"timestamp":" 946869379985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869380768","data":{"timestamp":" 946869380767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINYWA"," userResponse":" AKINYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869381016","data":{"timestamp":" 946869381015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869381920","data":{"timestamp":" 946869381920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMALIZA"," userResponse":" KUMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869382629","data":{"timestamp":" 946869382629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869385875","data":{"timestamp":" 946869385874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869387732","data":{"timestamp":" 946869387731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869394477","data":{"timestamp":" 946869394476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869396524","data":{"timestamp":" 946869396524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869400717","data":{"timestamp":" 946869400716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869402670","data":{"timestamp":" 946869402670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869405112","data":{"timestamp":" 946869405112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869407084","data":{"timestamp":" 946869407084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHANGAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869409572","data":{"timestamp":" 946869409571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869412020","data":{"timestamp":" 946869412020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869418715","data":{"timestamp":" 946869418715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869420481","data":{"timestamp":" 946869420480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869422558","data":{"timestamp":" 946869422558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMALIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869425950","data":{"timestamp":" 946869425950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869428102","data":{"timestamp":" 946869428101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869428668","data":{"timestamp":" 946869428667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869428921","data":{"timestamp":" 946869428921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869430170","data":{"timestamp":" 946869430170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHANGAZA"," userResponse":" KUSHANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869433645","data":{"timestamp":" 946869433644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869435578","data":{"timestamp":" 946869435578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869437116","data":{"timestamp":" 946869437116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869439170","data":{"timestamp":" 946869439170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHANGAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869441486","data":{"timestamp":" 946869441486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869441758","data":{"timestamp":" 946869441757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869442490","data":{"timestamp":" 946869442490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869443740","data":{"timestamp":" 946869443739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" WALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869444433","data":{"timestamp":" 946869444432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869445960","data":{"timestamp":" 946869445960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869446819","data":{"timestamp":" 946869446818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHA"," userResponse":" KUMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869447488","data":{"timestamp":" 946869447487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869447993","data":{"timestamp":" 946869447993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869448780","data":{"timestamp":" 946869448779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALALE"," userResponse":" ALALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869449743","data":{"timestamp":" 946869449742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869450500","data":{"timestamp":" 946869450500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAHAME"," userResponse":" WAHAME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869451131","data":{"timestamp":" 946869451130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869451680","data":{"timestamp":" 946869451679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869452345","data":{"timestamp":" 946869452345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869452583","data":{"timestamp":" 946869452583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869453285","data":{"timestamp":" 946869453285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869456104","data":{"timestamp":" 946869456104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869458251","data":{"timestamp":" 946869458250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869461959","data":{"timestamp":" 946869461959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869464255","data":{"timestamp":" 946869464255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869467387","data":{"timestamp":" 946869467387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869469850","data":{"timestamp":" 946869469850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869474750","data":{"timestamp":" 946869474750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869477281","data":{"timestamp":" 946869477281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869479696","data":{"timestamp":" 946869479695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869481924","data":{"timestamp":" 946869481924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869484398","data":{"timestamp":" 946869484398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869486714","data":{"timestamp":" 946869486713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAHAME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869488972","data":{"timestamp":" 946869488972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869491843","data":{"timestamp":" 946869491843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869496982","data":{"timestamp":" 946869496981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869498892","data":{"timestamp":" 946869498892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869501137","data":{"timestamp":" 946869501137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869503540","data":{"timestamp":" 946869503540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869504172","data":{"timestamp":" 946869504172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869505183","data":{"timestamp":" 946869505183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869506030","data":{"timestamp":" 946869506029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869506263","data":{"timestamp":" 946869506262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869506942","data":{"timestamp":" 946869506941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869507506","data":{"timestamp":" 946869507505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869510740","data":{"timestamp":" 946869510740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869513208","data":{"timestamp":" 946869513208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869515359","data":{"timestamp":" 946869515359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869517446","data":{"timestamp":" 946869517444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869519091","data":{"timestamp":" 946869519091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869521616","data":{"timestamp":" 946869521614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869523324","data":{"timestamp":" 946869523324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869525875","data":{"timestamp":" 946869525875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWACHIA"," userResponse":" WALIMWACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869526694","data":{"timestamp":" 946869526693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869526707","data":{"timestamp":" 946869526707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869528044","data":{"timestamp":" 946869528044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869528498","data":{"timestamp":" 946869528498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869529297","data":{"timestamp":" 946869529296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869532780","data":{"timestamp":" 946869532780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWACHIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869534337","data":{"timestamp":" 946869534337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869536415","data":{"timestamp":" 946869536415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869538433","data":{"timestamp":" 946869538433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869541164","data":{"timestamp":" 946869541163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869543641","data":{"timestamp":" 946869543641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869546089","data":{"timestamp":" 946869546088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869546463","data":{"timestamp":" 946869546463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869547929","data":{"timestamp":" 946869547928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869549972","data":{"timestamp":" 946869549971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUTA"," userResponse":" AKAKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869550706","data":{"timestamp":" 946869550706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869552191","data":{"timestamp":" 946869552190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOACHIWA"," userResponse":" ALIOACHIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869552425","data":{"timestamp":" 946869552424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869553438","data":{"timestamp":" 946869553438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZINGIRA"," userResponse":" MAZINGIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869553502","data":{"timestamp":" 946869553502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869554581","data":{"timestamp":" 946869554581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869555542","data":{"timestamp":" 946869555541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKIWA"," userResponse":" YAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869556332","data":{"timestamp":" 946869556331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVU"," userResponse":" TULIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869556865","data":{"timestamp":" 946869556865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869560696","data":{"timestamp":" 946869560695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869563405","data":{"timestamp":" 946869563405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869565972","data":{"timestamp":" 946869565972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOAMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869568053","data":{"timestamp":" 946869568052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869570419","data":{"timestamp":" 946869570419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869572818","data":{"timestamp":" 946869572818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOACHIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869574828","data":{"timestamp":" 946869574828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869577337","data":{"timestamp":" 946869577337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZINGIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869579373","data":{"timestamp":" 946869579373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869581780","data":{"timestamp":" 946869581780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869585141","data":{"timestamp":" 946869585141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869587272","data":{"timestamp":" 946869587272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869589708","data":{"timestamp":" 946869589707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869592544","data":{"timestamp":" 946869592543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869593164","data":{"timestamp":" 946869593163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869594158","data":{"timestamp":" 946869594158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMUA"," userResponse":" AKAAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869595257","data":{"timestamp":" 946869595256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAUA"," userResponse":" KUWAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869595690","data":{"timestamp":" 946869595690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869596590","data":{"timestamp":" 946869596589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869597860","data":{"timestamp":" 946869597859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869598351","data":{"timestamp":" 946869598350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869598370","data":{"timestamp":" 946869598370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869601500","data":{"timestamp":" 946869601500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869603407","data":{"timestamp":" 946869603406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869606006","data":{"timestamp":" 946869606006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869608107","data":{"timestamp":" 946869608107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869609992","data":{"timestamp":" 946869609991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869612339","data":{"timestamp":" 946869612339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869614446","data":{"timestamp":" 946869614446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869616138","data":{"timestamp":" 946869616138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869617976","data":{"timestamp":" 946869617975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869620124","data":{"timestamp":" 946869620124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869620940","data":{"timestamp":" 946869620939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869621214","data":{"timestamp":" 946869621214"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869621781","data":{"timestamp":" 946869621781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869621797","data":{"timestamp":" 946869621797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869625388","data":{"timestamp":" 946869625388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869628299","data":{"timestamp":" 946869628299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869629918","data":{"timestamp":" 946869629918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869631660","data":{"timestamp":" 946869631660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869635022","data":{"timestamp":" 946869635021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869637418","data":{"timestamp":" 946869637417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869637433","data":{"timestamp":" 946869637433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869638547","data":{"timestamp":" 946869638546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869639780","data":{"timestamp":" 946869639779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869641018","data":{"timestamp":" 946869641018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869641771","data":{"timestamp":" 946869641771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" FULANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869642820","data":{"timestamp":" 946869642819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPITA"," userResponse":" AKAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869643518","data":{"timestamp":" 946869643518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869644310","data":{"timestamp":" 946869644309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869644786","data":{"timestamp":" 946869644785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869644814","data":{"timestamp":" 946869644813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869645431","data":{"timestamp":" 946869645431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869646415","data":{"timestamp":" 946869646414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869648266","data":{"timestamp":" 946869648265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMCHINJA"," userResponse":" NITAMCHINJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869648796","data":{"timestamp":" 946869648795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869648822","data":{"timestamp":" 946869648822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869649294","data":{"timestamp":" 946869649293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869649980","data":{"timestamp":" 946869649980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIPATE"," userResponse":" NIPATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869650883","data":{"timestamp":" 946869650883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITOWEO"," userResponse":" KITOWEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869654857","data":{"timestamp":" 946869654857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869657332","data":{"timestamp":" 946869657332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869660294","data":{"timestamp":" 946869660293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869662675","data":{"timestamp":" 946869662675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869665411","data":{"timestamp":" 946869665411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869667843","data":{"timestamp":" 946869667843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869670336","data":{"timestamp":" 946869670336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869673356","data":{"timestamp":" 946869673356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869676207","data":{"timestamp":" 946869676207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869679306","data":{"timestamp":" 946869679306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869681741","data":{"timestamp":" 946869681740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869683995","data":{"timestamp":" 946869683995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869687825","data":{"timestamp":" 946869687824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869690544","data":{"timestamp":" 946869690544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMCHINJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869693238","data":{"timestamp":" 946869693238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869695075","data":{"timestamp":" 946869695075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869697115","data":{"timestamp":" 946869697115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869698815","data":{"timestamp":" 946869698815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIPATE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869701087","data":{"timestamp":" 946869701087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITOWEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869703400","data":{"timestamp":" 946869703400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMCHOMA"," userResponse":" AKAMCHOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869703684","data":{"timestamp":" 946869703684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869704378","data":{"timestamp":" 946869704378"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUKI"," userResponse":" MKUKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869705101","data":{"timestamp":" 946869705101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFA"," userResponse":" AKAFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869710187","data":{"timestamp":" 946869710187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMCHOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869711953","data":{"timestamp":" 946869711953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869713747","data":{"timestamp":" 946869713747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869715736","data":{"timestamp":" 946869715735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869718554","data":{"timestamp":" 946869718553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869719798","data":{"timestamp":" 946869719797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNA"," userResponse":" AKIMCHUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869720581","data":{"timestamp":" 946869720580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869721683","data":{"timestamp":" 946869721683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869722476","data":{"timestamp":" 946869722476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869723810","data":{"timestamp":" 946869723810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" IKITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869724244","data":{"timestamp":" 946869724244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869724678","data":{"timestamp":" 946869724678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869724921","data":{"timestamp":" 946869724921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869725396","data":{"timestamp":" 946869725395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869725413","data":{"timestamp":" 946869725413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869727467","data":{"timestamp":" 946869727467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINIUMIZE"," userResponse":" USINIUMIZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869728189","data":{"timestamp":" 946869728188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869729277","data":{"timestamp":" 946869729276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869732369","data":{"timestamp":" 946869732369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869734906","data":{"timestamp":" 946869734906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869736930","data":{"timestamp":" 946869736930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869739016","data":{"timestamp":" 946869739016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869741720","data":{"timestamp":" 946869741720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869744061","data":{"timestamp":" 946869744061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869745763","data":{"timestamp":" 946869745762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869747685","data":{"timestamp":" 946869747685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869749173","data":{"timestamp":" 946869749173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869750794","data":{"timestamp":" 946869750794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869752632","data":{"timestamp":" 946869752632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869755334","data":{"timestamp":" 946869755334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINIUMIZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869757722","data":{"timestamp":" 946869757721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869759822","data":{"timestamp":" 946869759822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869762308","data":{"timestamp":" 946869762308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869762532","data":{"timestamp":" 946869762532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869763596","data":{"timestamp":" 946869763596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMIUJIZA"," userResponse":" KIMIUJIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869764659","data":{"timestamp":" 946869764659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOKA"," userResponse":" AKATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869765242","data":{"timestamp":" 946869765242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869765505","data":{"timestamp":" 946869765505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869766078","data":{"timestamp":" 946869766078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869766095","data":{"timestamp":" 946869766095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869766847","data":{"timestamp":" 946869766847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869767371","data":{"timestamp":" 946869767371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869768504","data":{"timestamp":" 946869768504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJINATA"," userResponse":" KUJINATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869769128","data":{"timestamp":" 946869769128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869769573","data":{"timestamp":" 946869769572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869769796","data":{"timestamp":" 946869769796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869770730","data":{"timestamp":" 946869770730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869771075","data":{"timestamp":" 946869771074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869774422","data":{"timestamp":" 946869774422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869776330","data":{"timestamp":" 946869776330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869778613","data":{"timestamp":" 946869778613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMIUJIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869780701","data":{"timestamp":" 946869780701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869783333","data":{"timestamp":" 946869783332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869785086","data":{"timestamp":" 946869785086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869787051","data":{"timestamp":" 946869787051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869799629","data":{"timestamp":" 946869799629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869802488","data":{"timestamp":" 946869802488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869804836","data":{"timestamp":" 946869804836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869808017","data":{"timestamp":" 946869808016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJINATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869810374","data":{"timestamp":" 946869810373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869812801","data":{"timestamp":" 946869812801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869815148","data":{"timestamp":" 946869815148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869816840","data":{"timestamp":" 946869816839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869818754","data":{"timestamp":" 946869818754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869821043","data":{"timestamp":" 946869821043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869821978","data":{"timestamp":" 946869821977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869822698","data":{"timestamp":" 946869822697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869823649","data":{"timestamp":" 946869823649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869824257","data":{"timestamp":" 946869824257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869825015","data":{"timestamp":" 946869825015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869825491","data":{"timestamp":" 946869825491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869825958","data":{"timestamp":" 946869825957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869828633","data":{"timestamp":" 946869828633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869832024","data":{"timestamp":" 946869832024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869834978","data":{"timestamp":" 946869834978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869839965","data":{"timestamp":" 946869839964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869844785","data":{"timestamp":" 946869844785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869847520","data":{"timestamp":" 946869847520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869854018","data":{"timestamp":" 946869854018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869856010","data":{"timestamp":" 946869856010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869858744","data":{"timestamp":" 946869858743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869859525","data":{"timestamp":" 946869859522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869860724","data":{"timestamp":" 946869860723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHINJIA"," userResponse":" ALIMCHINJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869861240","data":{"timestamp":" 946869861239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869861827","data":{"timestamp":" 946869861826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869862462","data":{"timestamp":" 946869862461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869862657","data":{"timestamp":" 946869862656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUME"," userResponse":" DUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869864336","data":{"timestamp":" 946869864336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYENONA"," userResponse":" ALIYENONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869870332","data":{"timestamp":" 946869870332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869874671","data":{"timestamp":" 946869874670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869878718","data":{"timestamp":" 946869878718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHINJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869882033","data":{"timestamp":" 946869882032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869883969","data":{"timestamp":" 946869883969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869887648","data":{"timestamp":" 946869887648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869891923","data":{"timestamp":" 946869891923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869899479","data":{"timestamp":" 946869899479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYENONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869901857","data":{"timestamp":" 946869901857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869902082","data":{"timestamp":" 946869902081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869903030","data":{"timestamp":" 946869903029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMIUJIZA"," userResponse":" KIMIUJIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869903964","data":{"timestamp":" 946869903964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALA"," userResponse":" AKALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869905766","data":{"timestamp":" 946869905765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFURAHI"," userResponse":" AKAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869906450","data":{"timestamp":" 946869906449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869907078","data":{"timestamp":" 946869907077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869907282","data":{"timestamp":" 946869907282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869908241","data":{"timestamp":" 946869908240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869908869","data":{"timestamp":" 946869908869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869911902","data":{"timestamp":" 946869911902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869913706","data":{"timestamp":" 946869913705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869916114","data":{"timestamp":" 946869916114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMIUJIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869917967","data":{"timestamp":" 946869917967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869921006","data":{"timestamp":" 946869921006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869923576","data":{"timestamp":" 946869923575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869925984","data":{"timestamp":" 946869925984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869928015","data":{"timestamp":" 946869928014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869929979","data":{"timestamp":" 946869929978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869933804","data":{"timestamp":" 946869933804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869935813","data":{"timestamp":" 946869935813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869935976","data":{"timestamp":" 946869935976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 67274417-6cd1-4aa8-a6ea-9c6f78c0be1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869946672","data":{"timestamp":" 946869946672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" cc8d026a-6988-4246-96af-8c157c358cdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869951883","data":{"timestamp":" 946869951883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" cc8d026a-6988-4246-96af-8c157c358cdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869958195","data":{"timestamp":" 946869958194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" cc8d026a-6988-4246-96af-8c157c358cdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869971354","data":{"timestamp":" 946869971354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869971869","data":{"timestamp":" 946869971869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869972743","data":{"timestamp":" 946869972743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869973610","data":{"timestamp":" 946869973609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869977892","data":{"timestamp":" 946869977892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869978439","data":{"timestamp":" 946869978439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869979682","data":{"timestamp":" 946869979682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869980821","data":{"timestamp":" 946869980820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869981553","data":{"timestamp":" 946869981553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869986086","data":{"timestamp":" 946869986086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869986749","data":{"timestamp":" 946869986749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869988292","data":{"timestamp":" 946869988292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869988798","data":{"timestamp":" 946869988798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869994129","data":{"timestamp":" 946869994129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869995209","data":{"timestamp":" 946869995209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869996042","data":{"timestamp":" 946869996042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870002712","data":{"timestamp":" 946870002712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870003195","data":{"timestamp":" 946870003195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870005776","data":{"timestamp":" 946870005776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870008625","data":{"timestamp":" 946870008625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870010182","data":{"timestamp":" 946870010182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870014371","data":{"timestamp":" 946870014371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870015804","data":{"timestamp":" 946870015804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870016417","data":{"timestamp":" 946870016417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870021231","data":{"timestamp":" 946870021231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870022203","data":{"timestamp":" 946870022203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" va"," userResponse":" va"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870023253","data":{"timestamp":" 946870023252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870024052","data":{"timestamp":" 946870024052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870028036","data":{"timestamp":" 946870028035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870029283","data":{"timestamp":" 946870029282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870030346","data":{"timestamp":" 946870030346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870031212","data":{"timestamp":" 946870031212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870037276","data":{"timestamp":" 946870037276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870038407","data":{"timestamp":" 946870038406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870039423","data":{"timestamp":" 946870039422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870040364","data":{"timestamp":" 946870040363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870042587","data":{"timestamp":" 946870042587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870045718","data":{"timestamp":" 946870045718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870047768","data":{"timestamp":" 946870047768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870049390","data":{"timestamp":" 946870049390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870051191","data":{"timestamp":" 946870051191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870052055","data":{"timestamp":" 946870052055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870057045","data":{"timestamp":" 946870057044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870058142","data":{"timestamp":" 946870058142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870058958","data":{"timestamp":" 946870058958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870059457","data":{"timestamp":" 946870059457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870061755","data":{"timestamp":" 946870061754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 43192058-7ce8-40f0-9b13-e1ec7f0abc8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_vipepeo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870077287","data":{"timestamp":" 946870077286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870078184","data":{"timestamp":" 946870078184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870079017","data":{"timestamp":" 946870079016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870080199","data":{"timestamp":" 946870080199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870090576","data":{"timestamp":" 946870090576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870097119","data":{"timestamp":" 946870097118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870098212","data":{"timestamp":" 946870098212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870098717","data":{"timestamp":" 946870098717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870099042","data":{"timestamp":" 946870099042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870103055","data":{"timestamp":" 946870103055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870109150","data":{"timestamp":" 946870109150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870109809","data":{"timestamp":" 946870109808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870110333","data":{"timestamp":" 946870110333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870110866","data":{"timestamp":" 946870110866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870114032","data":{"timestamp":" 946870114032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870115098","data":{"timestamp":" 946870115098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870115712","data":{"timestamp":" 946870115712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870116121","data":{"timestamp":" 946870116120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870121977","data":{"timestamp":" 946870121977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870128597","data":{"timestamp":" 946870128597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870129477","data":{"timestamp":" 946870129477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870129944","data":{"timestamp":" 946870129944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870130268","data":{"timestamp":" 946870130268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870134176","data":{"timestamp":" 946870134176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870134965","data":{"timestamp":" 946870134965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870135706","data":{"timestamp":" 946870135706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870137273","data":{"timestamp":" 946870137272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870137588","data":{"timestamp":" 946870137588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870145808","data":{"timestamp":" 946870145808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870146839","data":{"timestamp":" 946870146839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870147030","data":{"timestamp":" 946870147030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870153592","data":{"timestamp":" 946870153592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870154125","data":{"timestamp":" 946870154125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870154425","data":{"timestamp":" 946870154425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870166170","data":{"timestamp":" 946870166170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870166827","data":{"timestamp":" 946870166826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870167157","data":{"timestamp":" 946870167157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870167740","data":{"timestamp":" 946870167740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870171539","data":{"timestamp":" 946870171539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870171978","data":{"timestamp":" 946870171978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870172320","data":{"timestamp":" 946870172320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870178699","data":{"timestamp":" 946870178698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870179207","data":{"timestamp":" 946870179206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870189370","data":{"timestamp":" 946870189370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870190357","data":{"timestamp":" 946870190357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870191600","data":{"timestamp":" 946870191600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870192782","data":{"timestamp":" 946870192782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870196430","data":{"timestamp":" 946870196430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870199279","data":{"timestamp":" 946870199279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6098641c-e023-4821-9d70-e977b2787dfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870214608","data":{"timestamp":" 946870214608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870214922","data":{"timestamp":" 946870214922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870215289","data":{"timestamp":" 946870215289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870215638","data":{"timestamp":" 946870215638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870219496","data":{"timestamp":" 946870219496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870219819","data":{"timestamp":" 946870219819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" va"," userResponse":" va"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870221053","data":{"timestamp":" 946870221053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870221384","data":{"timestamp":" 946870221384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870226142","data":{"timestamp":" 946870226142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870226564","data":{"timestamp":" 946870226564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870233353","data":{"timestamp":" 946870233353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870234300","data":{"timestamp":" 946870234300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870234760","data":{"timestamp":" 946870234760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870235241","data":{"timestamp":" 946870235241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870239741","data":{"timestamp":" 946870239740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870240580","data":{"timestamp":" 946870240580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870241312","data":{"timestamp":" 946870241312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870241645","data":{"timestamp":" 946870241645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870245227","data":{"timestamp":" 946870245227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870246309","data":{"timestamp":" 946870246309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870247883","data":{"timestamp":" 946870247883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870248749","data":{"timestamp":" 946870248749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870252756","data":{"timestamp":" 946870252756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870253879","data":{"timestamp":" 946870253879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870254395","data":{"timestamp":" 946870254395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870254628","data":{"timestamp":" 946870254628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870258604","data":{"timestamp":" 946870258604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870265030","data":{"timestamp":" 946870265030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870266020","data":{"timestamp":" 946870266020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870266845","data":{"timestamp":" 946870266845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870267253","data":{"timestamp":" 946870267253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870271962","data":{"timestamp":" 946870271961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870272499","data":{"timestamp":" 946870272499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870272882","data":{"timestamp":" 946870272882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870273224","data":{"timestamp":" 946870273224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870276940","data":{"timestamp":" 946870276940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870277521","data":{"timestamp":" 946870277521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870277863","data":{"timestamp":" 946870277862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870284134","data":{"timestamp":" 946870284133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870284642","data":{"timestamp":" 946870284641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870303756","data":{"timestamp":" 946870303756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870304478","data":{"timestamp":" 946870304477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870305070","data":{"timestamp":" 946870305070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870305487","data":{"timestamp":" 946870305487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870307391","data":{"timestamp":" 946870307390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 351f9d20-b255-4ddb-8aac-2f4d535f74c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870316371","data":{"timestamp":" 946870316371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6f930d27-7e37-474e-9ceb-f3e9da846ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870316603","data":{"timestamp":" 946870316602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6f930d27-7e37-474e-9ceb-f3e9da846ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870317576","data":{"timestamp":" 946870317575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6f930d27-7e37-474e-9ceb-f3e9da846ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870318862","data":{"timestamp":" 946870318861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6f930d27-7e37-474e-9ceb-f3e9da846ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870321071","data":{"timestamp":" 946870321070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6f930d27-7e37-474e-9ceb-f3e9da846ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870321132","data":{"timestamp":" 946870321131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 6f930d27-7e37-474e-9ceb-f3e9da846ac7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870334634","data":{"timestamp":" 946870334634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870334889","data":{"timestamp":" 946870334889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870335781","data":{"timestamp":" 946870335780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870336283","data":{"timestamp":" 946870336282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870336869","data":{"timestamp":" 946870336868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" VYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870337801","data":{"timestamp":" 946870337800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870338952","data":{"timestamp":" 946870338952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870339836","data":{"timestamp":" 946870339836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" WANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870340650","data":{"timestamp":" 946870340650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870340924","data":{"timestamp":" 946870340924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870341707","data":{"timestamp":" 946870341707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870344739","data":{"timestamp":" 946870344739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870346543","data":{"timestamp":" 946870346543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870348574","data":{"timestamp":" 946870348574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870350362","data":{"timestamp":" 946870350362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870352497","data":{"timestamp":" 946870352497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870354550","data":{"timestamp":" 946870354550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870357338","data":{"timestamp":" 946870357338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870359391","data":{"timestamp":" 946870359391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870362911","data":{"timestamp":" 946870362910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870373783","data":{"timestamp":" 946870373782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870375983","data":{"timestamp":" 946870375983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870377954","data":{"timestamp":" 946870377954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870378159","data":{"timestamp":" 946870378158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870379006","data":{"timestamp":" 946870379005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" MWITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870379856","data":{"timestamp":" 946870379855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870380517","data":{"timestamp":" 946870380516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870381150","data":{"timestamp":" 946870381150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870381729","data":{"timestamp":" 946870381728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870383062","data":{"timestamp":" 946870383061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" KUWAOGOFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870387695","data":{"timestamp":" 946870387695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870391331","data":{"timestamp":" 946870391331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870394400","data":{"timestamp":" 946870394400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870396441","data":{"timestamp":" 946870396440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870398850","data":{"timestamp":" 946870398850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870400655","data":{"timestamp":" 946870400655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870402277","data":{"timestamp":" 946870402277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870404822","data":{"timestamp":" 946870404822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870407217","data":{"timestamp":" 946870407216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870407688","data":{"timestamp":" 946870407688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870408555","data":{"timestamp":" 946870408554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" WALIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870409232","data":{"timestamp":" 946870409231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870409787","data":{"timestamp":" 946870409786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870410363","data":{"timestamp":" 946870410363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870413592","data":{"timestamp":" 946870413591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870415707","data":{"timestamp":" 946870415707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870420147","data":{"timestamp":" 946870420146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870422333","data":{"timestamp":" 946870422332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" WALIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870424204","data":{"timestamp":" 946870424204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870426964","data":{"timestamp":" 946870426963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870428945","data":{"timestamp":" 946870428944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870436453","data":{"timestamp":" 946870436453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870438211","data":{"timestamp":" 946870438211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870439419","data":{"timestamp":" 946870439418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" WALIWABEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870440452","data":{"timestamp":" 946870440452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870440675","data":{"timestamp":" 946870440675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870441788","data":{"timestamp":" 946870441788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" KUWAONDOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870442182","data":{"timestamp":" 946870442181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870444628","data":{"timestamp":" 946870444628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870446032","data":{"timestamp":" 946870446032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870452866","data":{"timestamp":" 946870452866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870455483","data":{"timestamp":" 946870455483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870457935","data":{"timestamp":" 946870457935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870460725","data":{"timestamp":" 946870460725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870463237","data":{"timestamp":" 946870463237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870465601","data":{"timestamp":" 946870465600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870466290","data":{"timestamp":" 946870466289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870467063","data":{"timestamp":" 946870467062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" PAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870467289","data":{"timestamp":" 946870467289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870468006","data":{"timestamp":" 946870468005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870468644","data":{"timestamp":" 946870468644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870472894","data":{"timestamp":" 946870472894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870473857","data":{"timestamp":" 946870473857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870479160","data":{"timestamp":" 946870479160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870482828","data":{"timestamp":" 946870482828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870486804","data":{"timestamp":" 946870486803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" WALIKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870488859","data":{"timestamp":" 946870488859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870492552","data":{"timestamp":" 946870492552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870494620","data":{"timestamp":" 946870494620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870496516","data":{"timestamp":" 946870496515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870497319","data":{"timestamp":" 946870497318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870498253","data":{"timestamp":" 946870498253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870501855","data":{"timestamp":" 946870501855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870507205","data":{"timestamp":" 946870507205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870508520","data":{"timestamp":" 946870508520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870517454","data":{"timestamp":" 946870517454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870522642","data":{"timestamp":" 946870522641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870525117","data":{"timestamp":" 946870525117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870525690","data":{"timestamp":" 946870525690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870526624","data":{"timestamp":" 946870526624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870527197","data":{"timestamp":" 946870527197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" JIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870533601","data":{"timestamp":" 946870533600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870535502","data":{"timestamp":" 946870535502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870538272","data":{"timestamp":" 946870538272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870539869","data":{"timestamp":" 946870539868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870541979","data":{"timestamp":" 946870541979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870542742","data":{"timestamp":" 946870542742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIGUMU"," userResponse":" VIGUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870543436","data":{"timestamp":" 946870543436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" KUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870544249","data":{"timestamp":" 946870544249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870545402","data":{"timestamp":" 946870545402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870549896","data":{"timestamp":" 946870549896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870552109","data":{"timestamp":" 946870552109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIGUMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870554935","data":{"timestamp":" 946870554935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870558473","data":{"timestamp":" 946870558473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870560378","data":{"timestamp":" 946870560378"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870562702","data":{"timestamp":" 946870562702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHAKA"," userResponse":" VICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870563595","data":{"timestamp":" 946870563595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIMEA"," userResponse":" VILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870564668","data":{"timestamp":" 946870564668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870564990","data":{"timestamp":" 946870564989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870565625","data":{"timestamp":" 946870565624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGO"," userResponse":" PENGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870565887","data":{"timestamp":" 946870565886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870566686","data":{"timestamp":" 946870566686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870569736","data":{"timestamp":" 946870569736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870571776","data":{"timestamp":" 946870571775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870577634","data":{"timestamp":" 946870577634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870579625","data":{"timestamp":" 946870579625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870591692","data":{"timestamp":" 946870591692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" VILIMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870604970","data":{"timestamp":" 946870604970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870609657","data":{"timestamp":" 946870609657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870614026","data":{"timestamp":" 946870614026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870615639","data":{"timestamp":" 946870615639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_231101"," gameId":" 1b124cee-c354-4a62-a8a1-18bd9532c885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}